Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
8094
Afrika Bambaataa, 1957-
600 cubic feet.
Vinyl records and other A/V Recordings, Financial Records, Manuscripts, Memorabilia, Photocopies, Photographs, Printed Materials, Publications.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Approximately 40,000 sound recordings representing Bambaataa's music collection from the 1970s to the present. The archive also includes books, documents, and files relating to the founding and spread of the Universal Zulu Nation; and videos, papers, and clothing.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Afrika Bambaataa is an American disc jockey, singer, and songwriter from the South Bronx, New York. Often called the “Godfather” of Hip Hop, Bambaataa has helped to define Hip Hop since it emerged in the South Bronx in the 1970s. One of a handful of Hip Hop's 1970s originators, Bambaataa gave Hip Hop its name, and was the first to define its core artistic elements - DJing, rapping, break dancing, and graffiti art - under one cultural umbrella. His cultural organization, the Universal Zulu Nation, has helped to spread Hip Hop culture throughout the world. His genre-defining 1982 song "Planet Rock" and subsequent electro-funk tracks have become icons of hip-hop and electronic music. In 2007 he was nominated for induction into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Approximately 40,000 sound recordings representing Bambaataa's music collection from the 1970s to the present. The archive also includes books, documents, and files relating to the founding and spread of the Universal Zulu Nation; and videos, papers, and clothing.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Afrika Bambaataa, 1957-; Universal Zulu Nation (Organization)
Subjects:
African American youth -- Social life and customs.; Disc jockeys.; Electronic music.; Funk (Music).; Hip-hop.; Hip-hop -- Influence.; Hip-hop -- History. -- United States; Music -- Social aspects.; Race relations.; Rap (Music); Rap (Music) -- Political aspects.; Rap musicians.; Hip-hop -- New York.; Rap (Music) -- New York.; Hip-hop; Rap (Music); Rap musicians; Social history
Places:
Bronx (New York, N.Y.) -- Social conditions -- 20th century.; New York (State) -- New York; New York (State) -- Bronx; United States
Form and Genre Terms:
History
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to collection restricted until completion of processing, with the exception of vinyl records that have been individually cataloged.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Manuscripts
a. School Papers and Assignments
b. Africa Trip
c. Soul Scrapbooks and Music Writing
d. Notebooks and Miscellaneous Manuscripts
e. Lyrics and Poems
f. Bronx River Neighborhood Center
g. Phone and Contact Lists
Series II. Flyers
Series III. Photographs
Series IV. Personal Papers
a. Personal Papers
b. Press About Bambaataa
c. Catalogs and Mail
Series V. Universal Zulu Nation Documents
a. Infinity Lessons
b. Administration
Series VI. Stage Costumes and Clothing
Series VII. Periodicals and Publications
a. Small Press Publications
b. Periodicals
c. Publications from 3410 De Reimer Ave. Bronx, NY
d. Other Publications
Series VIII. Moving images and audio recordings
a. Video cassettes
a. Audio cassettes
Series IX. Music collection
12 inch vinyl
Sureshots and altered/obscured
Numbered by Bambaataa
Annotated, not numbered (Alphabetical by artist)
A-D
E-H
I-L
L-O
P-S
T-Z
Numbers, unknown and various
Second alpha sequence
Cataloged individually
Not annotated (Alphabetical by artist)
A
B
C
D
E
F
G
H
I
J
K
L
M
N
O
P
Q
R
S
Afrika Bambaataa recordings
Renegades of Rhythm Tour
Test pressings and white labels (not yet cataloged)
Compilations (not yet cataloged)
7 inch vinyl
Numbered (not yet cataloged)
Annotated not numbered (not yet cataloged)
No annotations (not yet cataloged)
Acetates and lacquer discs
Cassettes (not yet cataloged)
CDs (not yet cataloged)
Series X. Ephemera
CONTAINER LIST
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Annotated, not numbered
      - A-D
        - Abdul, Paula - Forever your girl, 1988; SR-25005; Abdul, Paula (Box 21)
          Catalog # 1-90943; A-side Matrix # ST-VR-886961
          Virgin
          Beverly Hills, California
        - Adams & Fleisner - Electric boogie rhythm tracks, 1984; SR-25006; Adams & Fleisner (Box 21)
          Catalog # 841011; A-side Matrix # 841011 A S1C1
          Break Records
          Netherlands
        - Aerosmith - Live! Bootleg (disc one), 1978; SR-21111; Aerosmith (Box 21)
          In same jacket as # SR-21112; SR-21113. Double album, multiple copies.
          Catalog # AL 35565; A-side Matrix # AL-35565-1D
          Columbia
          New York, New York
        - Aerosmith - Live! Bootleg (disc one), 1978; SR-21112; Aerosmith (Box 21)
          In same jacket as # SR-21111; SR-21113. Double album, multiple copies.
        - Aerosmith - Live! Bootleg (disc two), 1978; SR-21113; Aerosmith (Box 21)
          In same jacket as # SR-21111; SR-21112. Double album, multiple copies.
          Catalog # AL 35565; A-side Matrix # AL-35565-1A
        - Afro Cuban Band - Have a real good time, 1979; SR-7693; Afro Cuban Band (Box 21)
          Catalog # CP-706; A-side Matrix # CP 706-SA-2
          Arista
        - Air Raid - Air raid, 1981; SR-25007; Air Raid (Box 21)
          Catalog # T-617; A-side Matrix # M-617-AS-A
          20th Century Fox Records
        - Ambassadeurs - Bobine, 1972; SR-7694; Ambassadeurs (Box 21)
          Catalog # MARC-229; A-side Matrix # MDVG 229A
          Marc Records
          Brooklyn, New York
        - April Wine - The nature of the beast, 1981; SR-25008; April Wine (Box 21)
          In same jacket as # SR-25007. Different discs.
          Catalog # SOO-12125; A-side Matrix # SOO-1-12125-Z2
          Capitol Records
          Hollywood, California
        - B-Movie - Remembrance day, 1981; SR-25009; B-Movie (Box 21)
          In same jacket as # SR-25006. Different discs.
          Catalog # DMX 437; A-side Matrix # DMX437 A1E PS 1-1
          DERAM
          London, United Kingdom
        - Archive - Londinium (disc one), 1996; SR-25010; Archive (Box 21)
          In same jacket as # SR-25011; SR-25012; SR-25013. Double album, multiple copies. Promo
          Catalog # ARKLP 1001; A-side Matrix # ARK LP 1001 A-1 EX
          Island Records
        - Archive - Londinium (disc two), 1996; SR-25011; Archive (Box 21)
          In same jacket as # SR-25010; SR-25012; SR-25013. Double album, multiple copies. Promo
          Catalog # ARKLP 1001; A-side Matrix # ARK LP 1001 C-2
        - Archive - Londinium (disc one), 1996; SR-25012; Archive (Box 21)
          In same jacket as # SR-25010; SR-25011; SR-25013. Double album, multiple copies. Promo
        - Archive - Londinium (disc one), 1996; SR-25013; Archive (Box 21)
          In same jacket as # SR-25010; SR-25011; SR-25012. Double album, multiple copies. Promo
        - Associates - Club country, 1982; SR-25014; Associates (Box 21)
          Catalog # ASC 2 T; A-side Matrix # ASC 2 T A2
          Associates
        - Aswad - Aswad, 1976; SR-25015; Aswad (Box 21)
          Catalog # ILPS-9399; A-side Matrix # ILPS-9399-A-P
          Los Angeles, California
        - Atension - Def on arrival, 1989; SR-25016; Atension (Box 21)
          Catalog # 91053-1; A-side Matrix # ST-IL 887255 A DMM
        - Au Pairs - Inconvenience; Pretty boys; plus remix of Headache, 1981; SR-7695; Au Pairs (Box 21)
          Catalog # HUM 8; A-side Matrix # HUM-8-A-1 LYN-10112-1 SC
          Human Records
          United Kingdom
        - Aurora Bora - JapRap, 1981; SR-7696; Aurora Bora (Box 21)
          Catalog # ARC-0239; A-side Matrix # ARC-0239-
          American City Records
          United States
        - Aurra - Send your love, 1981; SR-25017; Aurra (Box 21)
          In same jacket as # SR-25011. Different discs. Promo
          Catalog # SA 8538 (DJ); A-side Matrix # SA-8538-A1-Aurra
          Salsoul Records
        - Aurra - Send your love, 1981; SR-25018; Aurra (Box 21)
          In same jacket as # SR-25010. Different discs.
          Catalog # SA 8538; A-side Matrix # SA-8538-A-RE 1
        - Baby Huey - The Baby Huey story - the living legend, 1971; SR-25019; Baby Huey (Box 21)
          Catalog # CRS-8007; A-side Matrix # CRS-8007-A-1
          Curtom
        - Bad News Travels Fast - Look out, 1979; SR-25020; Bad News Travels Fast (Box 21)
          Promo
          Catalog # NBLP 7138 DJ; A-side Matrix # NBLP-7138-AS CP-2
          Casablanca
        - Balance & Terror - Let it flow; Intro; Represent, 1992; SR-25021; Balance & Terror (Box 21)
          Catalog # RPM 1000; A-side Matrix # RPM-1000-A
          RPM Records
        - Bassbin Twins - EP I, 1995; SR-7697; Bassbin Twins (Box 21)
          Catalog # L-45967; A-side Matrix # L-45967 BASS BIN TWINS SIDE A
          Bassbin Records
          California
        - Bataan, Joe - Afrofilipino, 1975; SR-25022; Bataan, Joe (Box 21)
          Catalog # KE 33471; A-side Matrix # P AL 33471-1F
          Epic
        - Beckett - Coming higher, 1978; SR-7698; Beckett (Box 21)
          Catalog # FR 0004; A-side Matrix # FR 0004 A
          First River Records
          St. Vincent
        - Belafonte, Harry - Calypso in brass, 1966; SR-25023; Belafonte, Harry (Box 21)
          Catalog # LPM 3658; A-side Matrix # TPRM-4269-2S
          RCA Victor
        - Belltones - In the mood, 1965; SR-25024; Belltones (Box 21)
          Catalog # BEL-1001; A-side Matrix # BEL-1001-A
          The Belltones Steel Orchestra of Trinidad
          Corona, New York
        - Bilingual Bandit - Latin twist issue 10, 2004; SR-25025; Bilingual Bandit (Box 21)
          Catalog # LATW-010; A-side Matrix # LATW-10 A1
          Latin Twist
        - Billy & the Beaters - Billy & the Beaters, 1981; SR-25026; Billy & the Beaters (Box 21)
          Catalog # AAA-10001; A-side Matrix # M-10001-A5 P1
          Alfa
        - Birdsong, Edwin - What it is, 1971; SR-7699; Birdsong, Edwin (Box 21)
          Catalog # 24-4071; A-side Matrix # POLP-80221-1A
          Polydor
        - Black Soul - Black Soul, 1977; SR-25027; Black Soul (Box 21)
          Catalog # BJ 5002 LP; A-side Matrix # BJ 5002 LP B
          Beam Junction
        - Blow Fly - On tour, 1974; SR-25028; Blow Fly (Box 21)
          Catalog # WW-2022; A-side Matrix # WW-2022-1
          Weird World
          Florida
        - Blue Rhythm Combo - The underdogs, 1975; SR-25029; Blue Rhythm Combo (Box 21)
          Catalog # BRU 001; A-side Matrix # BRU 001-A
          Underdog
          Barbados
        - Breathless - Nobody leaves this song alive, 1980; SR-25030; Breathless (Box 21)
          Catalog # SW-17041; A-side Matrix # SW-1-17041-Z7 M-1
          EMI America
        - Brecker Brothers - Don't stop the music, 1977; SR-25031; Brecker Brothers (Box 21)
          Catalog # ALD-02; A-side Matrix # ALD02-SA
        - Brides of Funkenstein - Never buy Texas from a cowboy, 1979; SR-25032; Brides of Funkenstein (Box 21)
          In same jacket as # SR-25022. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # SD 19261; A-side Matrix # STA-794407-C
          Atlantic
        - Brides of Funkenstein - Never buy Texas from a cowboy, 1979; SR-25033; Brides of Funkenstein (Box 21)
          In same jacket as # SR-25021. Multiple copies.
        - Brother D - Dib-be-dib-be-dize; How we gonna make the Black Nation rise?, 1980; SR-7700; Brother D; Collective Effort (Box 21)
          Catalog # CL-12-0001; A-side Matrix # CL-12-0001-A
          Clappers Records
        - Brown, Dennis - How can I leave you; Bubbling love, 1977; SR-25034; Brown, Dennis; Prince Mohammed (Box 21)
          Catalog #; A-side Matrix # DSR-5226-4-DT
          Joe Gibbs Record Globe
          Jamaica
        - Brown, James - People, 1980; SR-25035; Brown, James (Box 21)
          In same jacket as # SR-25025. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # PD-1-6258; A-side Matrix # PD-1-6258-AS-CP2
        - Brown, James - People, 1980; SR-25036; Brown, James (Box 21)
          In same jacket as # SR-25024. Multiple copies.
        - Brown, James - Revolution of the mind (disc two), 1971; SR-25037; Brown, James (Box 21)
          Catalog # PD-3003; A-side Matrix # POLP-80249-1D
        - Brown, James - Prisoner of love, 1983; SR-25038; Brown, James (Box 21)
          Re-issue
          Catalog # 813 491-1; A-side Matrix # 160 813491 1 1 380 POLYGRAM
          Paris, France
        - Brown, James - Nonstop!, 1981; SR-25039; Brown, James (Box 21)
          Catalog # PD-1-6318; A-side Matrix # PD 1 6318-AS-PW 1
        - Brown, James - Please, please, please, 1983; SR-25040; Brown, James; Famous Flames (Box 21)
          Catalog # 2489 194; A-side Matrix # 160 2489194 1 380 POLYGRAM
        - Brown, James - Soul syndrome, 1980; SR-25041; Brown, James (Box 21)
          Catalog # TK-615; A-side Matrix # TK-615-A-AM
          T.K. Records
          Hialeah, Florida
        - Brown, James - I got you (I feel good), 1983; SR-25042; Brown, James (Box 21)
          Catalog # 2489 196; A-side Matrix # 160 2489196 1 380 POLYGRAM
        - Brown, James - Excitement - Mr. Dynamite, 1983; SR-25043; Brown, James; Famous Flames (Box 21)
          Catalog # 2489 199; A-side Matrix # 160 2489199 1 380 POLYGRAM
        - Brown, James - It's a man's man's man's world, 1983; SR-25044; Brown, James (Box 21)
          Catalog # 2489 197; A-side Matrix # 160 2489197 1 380 POLYGRAM
        - Brown, James - Papa's got a brand new bag, 1983; SR-25045; Brown, James (Box 21)
          Catalog # 2489 195; A-side Matrix # 160 2489195 1 380 POLYGRAM
        - Brown, James - James Brown today & yesterday, 1965; SR-8083; Brown, James (Box 21)
          In same jacket as # SR-8084; SR-8085. Different discs.
          Catalog # MGS 27072; A-side Matrix # MG 27072A S1
          Smash Records
        - Brown, James - James Brown plays New Breed (the boo-ga-loo), 1966; SR-8084; Brown, James (Box 21)
          In same jacket as # SR-8083; SR-8085. Different discs.
          Catalog # MGS 27080; A-side Matrix # MG 27080A S1
        - Brown, James - A soulful Christmas, 1968; SR-8085; Brown, James (Box 21)
          In same jacket as # SR-8083; SR-8084. Different discs.
          Catalog # KS-12-1040; A-side Matrix # KSD-12-1040-A-5
          King Records
          Cincinnatti, Ohio
        - Brown, Jet - Only love can make it right; Dance the night away, 1979; SR-25046; Brown, Jet (Box 22)
          Catalog # PRO 112; A-side Matrix # PRO-11279-NP-425-S CP1
        - Byrd, Donald - Sexy dancer, 1982; SR-25047; Byrd, Donald; 125th Street, N.Y.C. Band (Box 22)
          Catalog # 0-67985; A-side Matrix # 0-67985 AS2 SP
          Elektra
        - Caldwell, Bobby - Jamaica, 1982; SR-7701; Caldwell, Bobby (Box 22)
          Catalog # PRO 182; A-side Matrix # PRO-182-81-NP-5810-PRC-C1-1 A
        - Calypso Rose - Leh we punta, 1987; SR-7702; Calypso Rose (Box 22)
          Catalog # GS2271; A-side Matrix # GS 2271-A-1
          Straker's Records
        - Calypso Rose - Sexy hot pants, 1972; SR-25048; Calypso Rose (Box 22)
          No entry in Discogs
          Catalog # PLS-7775; A-side Matrix # SR-7775 A 12-9-11
        - Calypso Rose - Pan in town, 1985; SR-25070; Calypso Rose (Box 22)
          Catalog # GS 2261; A-side Matrix # GS2261A
        - Calypso Rose - We rocking for Carnival, 1980; SR-25071; Calypso Rose (Box 22)
          Catalog # CR 251; A-side Matrix # CR251-A
          Charlie's Records
        - Cameo - The best of...pt. 1, 2004; SR-7703; Cameo (Box 22)
          In same jacket as # SR-7704; SR-7705. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # HP-020; A-side Matrix # HP-20-A
          House Party
        - Cameo - The best of...pt. 1, 2004; SR-7704; Cameo (Box 22)
          In same jacket as # SR-7703; SR-7705. Multiple copies.
        - Various - Krazy toons vol. 12, 1998; SR-7705 (Box 22)
          In same jacket as # SR-7703; SR-7704. Different discs.
          Catalog # KT-012; A-side Matrix # L-51190 MAIN SOURCE DIST. KT012 A
          Krazy Toons
        - Cameron, Jimmie - Song painters, 1980; SR-7706; Cameron, Jimmie; Cameron, Vella (Box 22)
          Catalog # JZ 36132; A-side Matrix # PAL-36132 3C
          Unlimited Gold
          Sherman Oaks, California
        - Capaldi, Jim - Electric Nights sampler, 1979; SR-7707; Capaldi, Jim (Box 22)
          Catalog # RPO 1015; A-side Matrix # T RPO1015 CT1 AS
          RSO
        - Capital Tax - The swoll package, 1993; SR-7708; Capital Tax (Box 22)
          Catalog # MCA-10784; A-side Matrix # MDI MCA-11560 MASTERDISK
          MCA Records
          Santa Monica, California
        - Captain & Tennille - Keeping our love warm, 1980; SR-7709; Captain & Tennille (Box 22)
          Catalog # NBLP 7250; A-side Matrix # NBLP-7250-AS PRCR-1-1
        - Captain Chameleon - Grab them cakes; Jive ol' fo, 1981; SR-7710; Captain Chameleon (Box 22)
          Catalog # JD-11807; A-side Matrix # LUM-123-10
          Millenium
        - Caress - Caress, 1979; SR-7717; Caress (Box 22)
          Catalog # RFC 3384; A-side Matrix # RFC 1 3384 LW2
          RFC Records
        - Carib Tokyo Steel Orchestra - 40 solid steel minutes, 1976; SR-25049; Carib Tokyo Steel Orchestra (Box 22)
          Catalog # CRS-0003; A-side Matrix # CRCS 0005-A
        - Carnes, Kim - Mistaken identity, 1981; SR-7718; Carnes, Kim (Box 22)
          Catalog # SO-17052; A-side Matrix # SO-1-17052-215
        - Caribbean Torpedos - Love, peace and unity, 1967; SR-25050; Caribbean Torpedos (Box 22)
          Catalog # ELPS-1119; A-side Matrix # ELPS-1119-S1
          Edmar Records
          Bermuda
        - CD III - Get tough, 1983; SR-7711; CD III (Box 22)
          In same jacket as # SR-7712. Multiple copies. Promo
          Catalog # PRL D598 AS; A-side Matrix # A-PRLD 672 A
          Prelude Records
        - CD III - Get tough, 1983; SR-7712; CD III (Box 22)
          In same jacket as # SR-7711. Multiple copies. Promo
        - CDLD - I'm the man, 1992; SR-25051; CDLD (Box 22)
          Catalog # PR-6; A-side Matrix # PR 6 A RE 2
          Planet Rock Music
          Bronx, New York
        - Central Line - Choice, 1983; SR-7719; Central Line (Box 22)
          Catalog # 422-814 733-1 M-1; A-side Matrix # 422 814 733-1 AS PRC C1-1 1
          Mercury
        - Central Line - Central Line, 1981; SR-7722; Central Line (Box 22)
          Catalog # SRM-A-4033; A-side Matrix # SRM 1 4033 AS HRM 1
        - Central Line - Don't tell me, 1981; SR-7725; Central Line (Box 22)
          Catalog # MERX 90; A-side Matrix # MERX 90 AH2 EM
        - Central Line - Time for some fun, 1983; SR-7726; Central Line (Box 22)
          Catalog # MERX 148; A-side Matrix # MERX 148 A 2 420
        - Cerrone - Cerrone IV - the golden touch, 1978; SR-7727; Cerrone (Box 22)
          Catalog # SD 5208; A-side Matrix # ST-CTN-784153-C
          Cotillion
        - Cerrone - Rock me, 1979; SR-7728; Cerrone (Box 22)
          Catalog # DSKO 194; A-side Matrix # ST-DK-37247-1 SP
        - Cerrone - Love in C minor, 1976; SR-7729; Cerrone (Box 22)
          Catalog # SD 9913; A-side Matrix # ST-CTN-773785-B
        - Cerrone - Supernature '86, 1986; SR-7730; Cerrone (Box 22)
          Catalog # MOLIF 5 P; A-side Matrix # MOLIF-5P-A1
          Music of Life
        - Certain Ratio - I'd like to see you again, 1982; SR-7731; Certain Ratio (Box 22)
          Catalog # FACT 65; A-side Matrix # FACT-65-A1
          Factory
        - Chagrin D'Amour - Chagrin D'Amour, 1982; SR-7732; Chagrin D'Amour (Box 22)
          Catalog # 200 422; A-side Matrix # 222 200 422 A POLYGRAM
          Barclay
          France
        - Chalice - Standard procedure, 1983; SR-7733; Chalice (Box 22)
          Catalog # PMLP 2; A-side Matrix # CHALICE-A
          Pipe Music
        - Champaign - How 'bout us, 1981; SR-7734; Champaign (Box 22)
          Catalog # JC 37008; A-side Matrix # PAL-37008 1G
        - Champs - Tequila, 1987; SR-7735; Champs (Box 22)
          Catalog # CH 227; A-side Matrix # CH 227A-1 B-9134 A-1
          Ace
        - Channel 2 - Slammin' at eleven, 1988; SR-7723; Channel 2 (Box 22)
          In same jacket as # SR-7724. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # 422 837 388-1; A-side Matrix # 422-837-388-1-A-SP1
          Wing Records
        - Channel 2 - Slammin' at eleven, 1988; SR-7724; Channel 2 (Box 22)
          In same jacket as # SR-7723. Multiple copies.
        - Charles, Tina - Rendezvous, 1977; SR-25052; Charles, Tina (Box 22)
          Catalog # PC 34807; A-side Matrix # AL 34807-1A
        - Charlie's Roots - The hammer, 1986; SR-7736; Charlie's Roots (Box 22)
          Catalog # CR 05; A-side Matrix # CRO 5B
        - Charme - Let it in, 1978; SR-7737; Charme (Box 22)
          Catalog # AFL1-3393; A-side Matrix # AFL1-3393A-1
        - Charo - Olé, olé, 1978; SR-7738; Charo (Box 22)
          Catalog # SA 8515 DJ; A-side Matrix # SA-8515-A-10
        - Charo - Stay with me; Hot love, 1978; SR-7739; Charo (Box 22)
          Catalog # SG 212 DJ; A-side Matrix # SG 212 A
        - Chasm, Anton - Children of the night; Electro fusion, 2002; SR-7741; Chasm, Anton (Box 22)
          Catalog # SA 002; A-side Matrix # SA002-A SCRUNCH
          Sound Alliance
          Philadelphia, Pennsylvania
        - Eon - Phaze test, 1996; SR-7742; Eon (Box 22)
          Test pressing
          Catalog # TRON 8; A-side Matrix # TRON 8 - A1
          Electron Industries
        - Checker, Chubby - Greatest hits, 1987; SR-7740; Checker, Chubby (Box 22)
          Catalog # ONE 1361; A-side Matrix # ONE-1361 A-1
          K-tel
        - Checker, Chubby - Your twist party (with the King of Twist), 1961; SR-7747; Checker, Chubby (Box 22)
          Catalog # P-7007; A-side Matrix # LP-P 7007-A2
          Parkway
        - Checker, Chubby - Limbo party, 1962; SR-7748; Checker, Chubby (Box 22)
          Catalog # P-7020; A-side Matrix # P-7020-A
        - Cheeseheadz - Take it to the maximum!, 1995; SR-7749; Cheeseheadz (Box 22)
          Catalog # TSS 005-5; A-side Matrix # 08 027534 20 1B1 TS 55
          360 Sound
        - Cheetah - Cheetah, 1981; SR-7750; Cheetah (Box 22)
          Catalog # AVI-6092; A-side Matrix # 031-6092 B
          AVI Records
        - Chemical Brothers - Dig your own hole (disc one), 1997; SR-7743; Chemical Brothers (Box 22)
          In same jacket as # SR-7744. Double album.
          Catalog # XDUSTLP2; A-side Matrix # YOU BE THE LINESMAN AND I'LL BE THE REFEREE XDUSTLP 2 A-01-01-1
          Freestyle Dust
        - Chemical Brothers - Dig your own hole (disc two), 1997; SR-7744; Chemical Brothers (Box 22)
          . Double album.
          Catalog # XDUSTLP2; A-side Matrix # TIME FOR A TIE STRAIGHTENER XDUSTLP 2 C-01-01-1
        - Chemical Brothers - Dig your own hole (disc one), 1997; SR-7745; Chemical Brothers (Box 22)
        - Chemical Brothers - Dig your own hole (disc two), 1997; SR-7746; Chemical Brothers (Box 22)
        - Chemical Brothers - Loops of fury, 1996; SR-7751; Chemical Brothers (Box 22)
          Catalog # ASW 6174-6; A-side Matrix # TW-ASZ-6174-SIDE 1
          Astralwerks
        - Chemical Brothers - Leave home, 1995; SR-7752; Chemical Brothers (Box 22)
          Catalog # CHEMST1; A-side Matrix # MIKE'S - THE EXCHANGE CHEMST 1 A-1-1-
        - Chemical Brothers - Block rockin' beats, 1997; SR-7753; Chemical Brothers (Box 22)
          Catalog # CHEMST5; A-side Matrix # MIKE'S - THE EXCHANGE CHEMST 5 A-01-01-1
        - Chemical Brothers - Exit planet dust (disc one), 1995; SR-7754; Chemical Brothers (Box 23)
          Catalog # XDUSTLP1; A-side Matrix # TO ALL THE TRUE FREE STYLE DJS WHO PLAY FREESTYLE AND FREESTYLE ALONE! XDUSTLP 1 A-1-1-1
        - Chemical Brothers - Exit planet dust (disc two), 1995; SR-7755; Chemical Brothers (Box 23)